<resources>
    <string name="app_name">chapter3</string>
    <string name="textview"><b>Computer science</b>Coding, often referred to as programming, is the process of creating instructions for computers to perform specific tasks. These instructions are written in programming languages, such as Python, Java, C++, and JavaScript. Coding involves the use of syntax and logical structures to develop software applications, websites, and systems that can execute various functions from simple calculations to complex data processing.\n

The essence of coding lies in problem-solving. Coders analyze problems, break them down into manageable parts, and devise algorithms to solve them. These algorithms are then translated into code that computers can interpret and execute. The process typically includes writing, testing, debugging, and maintaining code to ensure it works efficiently and correctly.\n
\n
Coding is foundational in the tech industry, driving innovation in fields such as artificial intelligence, cybersecurity, web development, and mobile app development. It empowers individuals to create technology solutions that can improve productivity, enhance communication, and drive business growth.\n
\n
Learning to code fosters critical thinking, logical reasoning, and creativity. As technology continues to evolve, coding skills are becoming increasingly valuable across various industries, making it an essential skill for the modern workforce. Whether developing software, automating tasks, or analyzing data, coding enables individuals to leverage the power of computers to solve real-world problems\n.

        Coding, often referred to as programming, is the process of creating instructions for computers to perform specific tasks. These instructions are written in programming languages, such as Python, Java, C++, and JavaScript. Coding involves the use of syntax and logical structures to develop software applications, websites, and systems that can execute various functions from simple calculations to complex data processing.\n

The essence of coding lies in problem-solving. Coders analyze problems, break them down into manageable parts, and devise algorithms to solve them. These algorithms are then translated into code that computers can interpret and execute. The process typically includes writing, testing, debugging, and maintaining code to ensure it works efficiently and correctly.\n
\n
Coding is foundational in the tech industry, driving innovation in fields such as artificial intelligence, cybersecurity, web development, and mobile app development. It empowers individuals to create technology solutions that can improve productivity, enhance communication, and drive business growth.\n
\n
Learning to code fosters critical thinking, logical reasoning, and creativity. As technology continues to evolve, coding skills are becoming increasingly valuable across various industries, making it an essential skill for the modern workforce. Whether developing software, automating tasks, or analyzing data, coding enables individuals to leverage the power of computers to solve real-world problems\n.

        The essence of coding lies in problem-solving. Coders analyze problems, break them down into manageable parts, and devise algorithms to solve them. These algorithms are then translated into code that computers can interpret and execute. The process typically includes writing, testing, debugging, and maintaining code to ensure it works efficiently and correctly.\n
\n
Coding is foundational in the tech industry, driving innovation in fields such as artificial intelligence, cybersecurity, web development, and mobile app development. It empowers individuals to create technology solutions that can improve productivity, enhance communication, and drive business growth.\n
\n
Learning to code fosters critical thinking, logical reasoning, and creativity. As technology continues to evolve, coding skills are becoming increasingly valuable across various industries, making it an essential skill for the modern workforce. Whether developing software, automating tasks, or analyzing data, coding enables individuals to leverage the power of computers to solve real-world problems\n.

    </string>
</resources>